<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<news>
    <item title="Ela Platform 2013.3 is out" date="2013-10-02">
        <![CDATA[Ela Platform 2013.3 contains many important bug fixes in Ela and Elide, Ela intergrated environment.
        This version of platform also introduces a new version of Ela that allows to use pattern matching in do-notation.]]>
    </item>
    
    <item title="New project hosting platform" date="2013-10-02">
        <![CDATA[Google Code used to be a primary project hosting for Ela project. However, Google is currently
        deprecating its download services, which is a pretty serious issue for projects that require to publish
        binary releases from time to time. As a result Ela project is now moving to CodePlex: <a target="_blank" href="https://ela.codeplex.com/">ela.codeplex.com</a>.]]>
    </item>

    <item title="Ela Platform 2013.2 is out" date="2013-04-16">
        <![CDATA[Ela Platform 2013.2 includes a new version of Ela with a refactored and improved 'do' 
        notation (which now supports 'let' bindings in Haskell style). Also this version of Platform comes 
        with a new release of standard library which contains several new additions including an IO monad.]]>
    </item>

    <item title="Ela Platform 2013.1 is out" date="2013-02-13">
        <![CDATA[Ela Platform 2013.1 comes with a new version of Ela (0.12.1) and an updated library.
        This is an experimental release that provides a support for monadic programming in Ela including
        monadic classes in standard library and a Haskell style 'do' notation.]]>
    </item>

    <item title="Ela Platform 2012.9 is out" date="2012-09-03">
        <![CDATA[Ela Platform 2012.9 comes with a new major version of Ela (0.12) that provides a better
        support for implicit laziness, negative numeric literals, pattern matching validation for overlapping,
        bang patterns, type constraints for parameters of algebraic types constructors and more. This version
        of platform also features a significant update to the standard library.]]>
    </item>

    <item title="A new version of the book: Ela, dynamic functional language" date="2012-08-28">
        <![CDATA[A new version (0.6) of the book <i>Ela, dynamic functional language</i> is available. This book
        describes an upcoming version of Ela (0.12) and has a lot of corrections and amendments. This version
        of a book also contains new chapters about algebraic types and type classes.]]>
    </item>
    <item title="Ela Platform 2012.8 is out" date="2012-08-14">
            <![CDATA[
        Ela Platform 2012.8 includes a new version of Ela (0.11.2), which introduces a major new feature -
        overloading by return type. Also Ela Platform 2012.8 features a significant update to Ela standard
        library with new classes, functions and modules.
        ]]>
    </item>

</news>